Shiya.
Will we
meet again?
Pei
Song.
Hello, Mr. Pei.
Mr. Pei.
Here is your boutonniere.
No, thanks.
I'll do it myself.
Thank you.
He's attending his ex-wife's wedding
and wearing a family boutonniere.
Song Shiya's parents have passed away.
Who will walk her down the aisle?
He must be here to crash the wedding.
Why are you so late?
Did Shiya choose this music?
Yes.
It sounds terrible.
Fang Jingyan.
This is a wedding.
It's inappropriate for you to wear all black.
I think
you're the inappropriate one.
I'm here to mourn Shiya's love.
This is
the funeral of her love.
Shiya.
Ambulance!
Call an ambulance!
Hold on, Shiya.
Don't be sad.
We will meet again.
Shiya.
It's okay. Hold on.
The ambulance will be here soon.
Shiya.
Don't fall asleep,
Choose a good song.
Luckily, on a day like this,
there is such an opportunity.
Mr. Pei,
you're awake.
There's a huge traffic jam ahead.
We will likely be late
for Miss Shiya's wedding.
Good thing it was just a dream.
How long have I been asleep?
You fell asleep as soon as you got in the car.
What's next?
Starting next week,
there will be new programs
embarking on a new journey.
Lastly, I want to say thank you
and dedicate this last song to you.
There's no time.
I'll go by myself.
Mr. Pei.
This is just like in my dream.
Hello, Mr. Pei.
Mr. Pei.
Why is it exactly the same as my dream?
Hello, Mr. Pei.
This is your boutonniere.
He came to his ex-wife's wedding.
Song Shiya's parents have passed away.
A boutonniere for family members.
This one is exactly the same too.
Shiya.
Don't go up.
Shiya, you'll die.
Shiya.
Calm down.
Don't go up.
Pei Song.
Shiya.
You really can't go over there.
Let me go up.
Mr. Pei.
Shiya.
Pei Song.
Mr. Pei.
Shiya.
Is it a dream again?
December 20th.
This date...
Baby Shiya,
I really don't understand you.
You just crawled out of the grave of love.
Why are you jumping back in?
Maybe this one is Mr. Right.
Exactly.
Congratulations, Shiya,
on ending your single life again.
Congratulations.
All right, congratulations.
Thank you.
Come here.
What's wrong?
You seem distracted.
How could I be?
I'm getting married tomorrow.
What could happen today?
Hello?
Jingyan.
Where are you and Shiya?
Pei Song,
you're going a bit too far.
Today is Shiya's bachelorette party before her wedding.
Is it appropriate for her ex-husband to come?
Whether it's appropriate or not,
tell me the address.
What, do you regret it?
Want to win her back now?
Yes.
Tell me the address.
Which dress are you planning to wear for your wedding?
I think the one you recommended is pretty good.
Baby Shiya.
You look so beautiful today.
It's alright.
Are you excited?
Come on.